

NAUFAL DAWAM DZIKRILLAH

Junior Software Engineer

Phone : (+)62 882 9826 6676

E-mail: naufal.dawam.dz@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/naufal-dawam-dzikrillah-920168170/

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I've worked as a developer for over 2 years, with experience in both the backend and the frontend department level junior to middle. I am currently looking for a full time position in the field of frontend or backend development or IT position, with the hope of adding to kick start my career, broadening my horizons in the IT world and strengthening my knowledge base.

EDUCATION FORMAL

SMK INFORMATIKA YASMA

2014 - 2017

Informatics & Network Engineering

EDUCATION NON-FORMAL

BOOTCAMP PARTICIPANT JAVA PT TUJUH SEMBILAN

2019

- Deepen the basic knowledge of the Java programming language
- Received an internship invitation at Mola TV for 6 months.
- Completed the training in 2 months earlier than the specified time, which is 3 months

BOOTCAMP LARAVEL YBM PLN

2019

- Learn about programming language Laravel
- Create web app for record student Pesantren Tahfidz Enterprenuer Cisarua
- Get a job offer at PT Tujuh Sembilan in Bandung, West Java

BOOTCAMP PARTICIPANT BACKEND DEVELOPPER GOLANG ALTERRA ACADEMY

May 2022

Deepen the basic knowledge of the Golang, SQL, Unit Test

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

CV Cipta Indah Karya Sportindo

August 2020 - Sept 2021

- Technical Assistant
 - Manage databases and filling system a company including office data, staff and projects that have been implemented
 Collect and file expenses from 2019,2020,2021 (Such as expenditure documents, income, tenders, work packages, etc)
 - Manage employee payroll, both monthly employees to daily employees
 - Manage heavy equipment rental list
 - In addition to doing jobdesk as a personal assistant, I help companies with digital innovations, such as: making landing
 pages for companies, making field recording assistant applications via web applications to reduce paper usage (Example of
 landing pages made: https://webciks-v2-fix.vercel.app/)

PT Padepokan Tujuh Sembilan

June 2020 - July 2020

Technical Writer

- Determine the needs of programmers who will receive technical documentation
- Study sample applications and talk further with project managers and programmers
- Work with technical staff to make the application easier to use with short but easy to understand instructions
- Organize and write supporting documents for the application to be made using photos, pictures, and diagrams
- Determine the appropriate medium to convey the message to the programmer, such as manual writing or video
- Revise the document when an update related to the application is made

Intern PT Global Media Visual (Mola.tv)

Jan 2020 - June 2020

- Software Engineer
 - Developed front end experiences using React with TypeScript.
 - Make sure the web page builds can run quickly.
 - Develop various features on the web or application to improve customers experience.
 - Create code that can be reused for future use.
 - Create a web version guestbook for the office.
 - Make sure there are no bugs that can interfere with performance of the website or application.
 - Developed tools for internal use.
 - Fixed issues present on production build and optimized for multiple devices.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

OSIS SMK INFORMATIKA YASMA

2016 - 2017

Student Council Treasurer

- Become Treasurer
- Raise funds for the success of the celebration of independence and religious holidays
- · Be a committee in various school events

BOY SCOUT SMK INFORMATIKA YASMA

2015 - 2017

Scoutmaster Assistant SMK INFORMATIKA YASMA

- Become an assistant scout coach in terms of teaching
- Become an assistant scout coach in terms of activities outside of school, such as basic leadership training activities

PROJECT / VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Guestbook PT Global Media Visual (Mola.tv)

2020

Web application for guest at PT Global Media Visual (Mola.tv)

- Create a guest application for the company PT Global Media Visual (Mola.tv) using the typescript programming language
- Checking whether it is in accordance with the API that has been provided
- Check the running of the program to avoid bugs
- Make good and correct code so that in the future the next programmer will understand

Agenda Santri For Islamic Boarding School Tahfidz Quran YBM PLN (2019) Web application student agenda

2019

- Create an application to record the student agenda through the website (Using the Laravel 7) framework
- Helping the ustad in terms of time flexibility in managing the santri agenda
- In addition to the cleric who can see the schedule of students/students, they are also given the convenience of accessing the agenda
- Ustad and students are given different roles (Ustad can perform the CRUD feature, but students can only read)

Scoutmaster Junior High School Nurul Hidayah Jeruk Purut (2015 – 2017) Scoutmaster JHS MTS NH

2015 - 2017

- Become an assistant builder of ceremonies in carrying out scouting activities at school and outside school
- Besides just being an assistant, I also teach and become my side job when outside of school

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

SKILLS

Ms. Office : Ms. Word, Ms. Excel, Ms. Powerpoint.

Front end : React.

Back end : Java, Golang.

Design Tools: Corel, Photoshop, Figma, XD.

Editing Video : Adobe Product.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Indonesian (Native Proficiency)
- English (Basic)